Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Staff Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Holmes, Robert B., 1968-1992
  - Topical Files
    - 1990
      - Minority Student Data Requests (Box 267)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 267)
      - Orientation, Office of, 2 folders (Box 267)
      - Payment Plans (Box 267)
      - Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 267)
      - Registrar, Office of the
        - General, 2 folders (Box 267)
        - Closed Course (Box 267)
        - Grade Processing (Box 267)
        - Hold Credit (Box 267)
        - Identification Cards (Box 267)
        - Quality of Student Life (Box 267)
        - Residency (Box 267)
        - Retention Reports (Box 267)
        - Standardization of Data for Unit Analysis (SODUA) (Box 267)
      - Reporting to High Schools (Box 267)
      - Retention (Box 267)
      - Scheduling Office (Box 267)
      - Speeches, 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 268)
      - Spring Visitation for Students of Color (SVSC)/Minority Student Spring Visitation Program (Box 268)
      - Student Services (Box 268)
      - Study Abroad (Box 268)
      - Summer Programs (Box 268)
      - Surveys (Box 268)
      - Testing Issues (Box 268)
      - Transfers of Funds (Box 268)
      - University Cultural Center (Box 268)
      - University Information Systems (UIS) Costs and Charging (Box 268)
      - Vest, Charles (Provost) (correspondence with) (Box 268)
      - Vice President's Coordinating Group (Box 268)
      - Visitors' Center, 1986-1991 (Box 268)
    - 1991
      - Academic Services Units-Budgets, 1990/91
        - General (Box 268)
        - Admissions, Office of (Box 268)
        - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 268)
        - Financial Aid, Office of
          - General (Box 268)
          - Financial Aid Programs (Box 268)
        - Orientation Office (Box 268)
        - Registrar, Office of the (Box 268)
        - Scheduling Office (Box 268)
      - Admissions, Office of
        - General (Box 268)
        - Admissions Advisory Committee, Undergraduate (Box 268)
        - Admissions Cases (Box 285)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2076 ]
        - Budget, 1991/92 (Box 268)
        - Community Colleges (Box 269)
        - Mission Statement (Box 269)
        - Preferred Admissions (Box 269)
        - Procedures (Box 269)
        - Publications (Box 269)
        - Readmissions (Box 269)
        - Systems (Box 269)
        - Targets
          - General, 2 folders (Box 269)
          - Cumulative Applications and Admissions (Box 269)
      - Athletics
        - General (Box 269)
        - Athletic Admissions Cases and Appeals (Box 285)
      - Attrition Studies (Box 269)
      - Calendar, University (Box 269)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP)
        - General (Box 269)
        - Director Search (Box 285)
      - Data Systems Center (DSC) Supervisory Group (Box 269)
      - Detroit Public Schools/University of Michigan
        - Collaboration Committee, 1987-1991 (Box 269)
        - Dance Outreach Program (Box 269)
        - Detroit Compact, 1990-1992 (Box 269)
        - Dewey Center Community Writing Project (Box 269)
        - Mackenzie High School/U of M Writing Program, 1989-1991 (Box 269)
        - Retention Committee, 1987 (Box 269)
      - Equity, Salary (Box 269)
      - Fees, University Committee on Student (Box 269)
      - Financial Aid, Office of
        - General, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 269)
        - Advisory Committee, University Financial Aid (Box 269)
        - Financial Aid Programs (General Fund) (Box 269)
        - Fiscal Planning Group (Box 269)
        - Fundraising (Box 269)
        - Legislation (State and Federal) (Box 269)
        - Michigan Annual Giving (MAG) Program (Box 270)
        - Minority Aid Programs (Box 270)
        - Systems Development, 1990-1992 (Box 270)
        - Wade H. McCree, Jr. Incentive Scholarship Program (Box 270)
      - Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education (FIPSE) (Box 270)
      - Graduation Rates (Box 270)
      - Housing (Box 270)
      - Information Technology Policy Committee (ITPC) (Box 270)
      - Kuwait/Iraq, Students from (Box 270)
      - Marygrove College (Box 270)
      - Military Duty (by students in Gulf War) (Box 270)
      - Minority Degrees and Enrollment (Box 270)
      - Minority Student Data Requests (Box 270)
      - Official Third Week Count Project (O3WC) (Box 270)
      - Ombudsman's Office (Box 270)
      - Orientation, Office of (Box 270)
      - Payment Plans (Box 270)
      - Peace Corps (Box 270)
      - Presidents Council State Universities of Michigan (Box 270)
      - Press Releases (Box 270)
      - Regents, Board of (Box 270)
      - Registrar, Office of the
        - General (Box 270)
        - Hold Credits (Box 270)
        - Residency (Box 270)
      - Retention (Box 270)
      - Retreat, Student and Academic Services (Box 270)
      - Retrieval Conference "Admitting an Academically Talented and Multicultural Student Body" (Box 270)
      - Scheduling Office (Box 270)
      - Seltzer (Rob) Dissertation Committee (Box 285)
      - Siar Bossard Consulting Firm (Box 270)
        (re: France's university system and the French Ministry of Education)
      - Student Account System Development (Box 270)
      - Student Services (Box 270)
      - Study Abroad (Box 270)
      - Summer Programs (Box 270)
      - Surveys (Box 270)
      - Transfers of Funds (Box 270)
      - Vice President's Coordinating Group (Box 270)
      - Visitors Center (Box 270)
    - 1991-1992
      - Academic Services Board (ASB) (Box 271)
      - Administrative Technology Working Group (ATWG)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 271)
        - Costs (Box 271)
      - Admissions, Office of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 271)
        - Advisory Committee (Box 271)
        - Application Fee (Box 271)
        - Budget (Box 271)
        - Community Colleges
          - General (Box 271)
          - Washtenaw Community College (Box 271)
          - Wayne County Community College (Box 271)
        - Minorities (Box 271)
        - Publications (Box 271)
        - System (Box 271)
        - Targets (Box 271)
      - Alumni Association (Box 271)
      - Attrition Studies
        - General (Box 271)
        - Historical Reports, 1979-1989 (Box 271)
      - Audit Report (State) on Enrollment (Box 271)
      - Budget Request, Academic Services (Box 271)
      - Calendar Review Committee (Box 271)
      - Capital Campaign (Box 271)
      - Commission on Recruitment, Success, and Graduation of Students of Color (Box 271)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP)
        - General (Box 271)
        - Budget (Box 272)
        - Systems Project (Box 272)
      - Data Systems Center (DSC) Supervisory Group (Box 272)
      - Enrollment Working Group
        - General (Box 272)
        - Statistics and Targets, 5 folders (Box 272)
      - Executive Computing Committee (Box 272)
      - Fees, University Committee on Student (Box 272)
      - Financial Aid, Office of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 272)
        - Advisory Committee, University Financial Aid (Box 272)
        - Appeals Board and Procedures (Box 272)
        - Budget (Box 272)
        - Fiscal Planning Committee (Box 272)
        - Fundraising (Box 272)
        - Legislation (State and Federal) (Box 272)
        - Michigan Annual Giving (MAG) Program (Box 272)
        - Minority Aid Programs (Box 273)
        - Systems Development, Joint Applications, 2 folders (Box 273)
        - Wade H. McCree, Jr. Incentive Scholarship Program (Box 273)
      - Graduation Rates (Box 273)
      - Johnson, Harold R. (Committee to Review University Programs in Minority Affairs and Services) (Box 273)
      - M-Quality (Total Quality Management) (and 1 volume) (Box 273)
      - Minority Counts (Box 273)
      - Minority Student Data Requests (Box 273)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 273)
      - Official Third Week Counts (O3WC) (Box 273)
      - Orientation, Office of (Box 273)
      - Press Releases (Box 273)
      - Prisoners (Box 273)
      - Regents, Board of (Box 273)
      - Registrar, Office of the
        - General (Box 273)
        - Budget (Box 273)
        - Hold Credit (Box 273)
        - Registrar Search (Box 285)
        - Residency (Box 273)
        - Residency Appeals (Box 285)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2077 ]
      - Reporting to High Schools (Box 273)
      - Scheduling Office
        - General (Box 273)
        - Budget (Box 273)
      - Space (Student Activities Building) (Box 273)
      - Spring Visitation (Box 273)
      - Student Account System Development (Box 273)
      - Student Services (Box 273)
      - Study Abroad (Box 273)
      - Summer Programs (Box 273)
      - Surveys (Box 273)
      - Transfers of Funds (Box 274)
      - Visitor Parking, Visitor Relations (Box 274)
      - Visitors' Center (Box 274)
      - Whitmore Lake Public Schools Renaissance Program (Box 274)
    - 1971-1992
      - Academic Services, Administration of, 1971; 1991 (Box 274)
      - Administrative Technology Working Group (ATWG), 1991-1992 (Box 274)
      - Admissions, Office of
        - Admissions System
          - Consultants, 1984 (Box 274)
          - Costs, 1987-1992 (Box 274)
        - Cook Project, 1989-1991 (Box 274)
        - Director of Undergraduate Admissions Search, 1987-1988 (Box 285)
        - High School Statistics, 1988-1991 (Box 274)
        - Minorities, 1987-1988 (Box 274)
        - Personnel, 1988-1990 (Box 285)
        - Reports, 1984-1991 (Box 274)
        - Shaw, R. (Director), Meetings with, 1991 (Box 274)
        - Targets, 1991 (Box 274)
        - Transfer Student Policy, 1990 (Box 274)
      - Affirmative Action, 1986-1990 (Box 274)
      - Allen, Walter (research re: minority students), 1981-1990; 2 folders (Box 274)
      - ARS (Academic Recognition Scholarship) Program, 1990 (Box 274)
      - Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 274)
      - Asian Issues, 1984-1988 (Box 274)
      - Athletics (includes NCAA reports), 1987-1991 (Box 274)
      - Attrition, 1982-1989 (Box 275)
      - Budgets, 1992-1993
        - General (Box 275)
        - Admissions, Office of (Box 275)
        - Comprehensive Studies Program (Box 275)
        - Financial Aid, Office of (Box 275)
        - Orientation Office (Box 275)
        - Registrar's Office (Box 275)
        - Scheduling Office (Box 275)
      - Chemistry Department, 1981-1989 (Box 275)
      - Chesler, Mark (Program on Conflict Management Alternatives), 1988-1989 (Box 275)
      - Commission on Minority Student Recruitment, Success, and Graduation, 1990 (Box 275)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (Terrance Brown), 1989-1990 (Box 275)
      - Enrollment Decision Project
        - General, 1982-1992 (Box 275)
        - Reports, 1983-1989; 2 folders (Box 275)
      - Financial Aid, Office of
        - General, 1984-1989 (Box 275)
        - Appeals Process, 1990-1991 (Box 275)
        - HR-11 Report, 1988-1989 (Box 275)
        - Program Review, 1983-1986 (Box 275)
        - Schools and Colleges (requests from)
          - Architecture and Urban Planning, 1975-1985 (Box 275)
          - Art, 1975-1984 (Box 275)
          - Business Administration, 1975-1984 (Box 275)
          - Dentistry, 1978-1986 (Box 275)
          - Education, 1975-1985 (Box 276)
          - Engineering, 1975-1985 (Box 276)
          - Information and Library Science, 1975-1986 (Box 276)
          - Law, 1975-1986 (Box 276)
          - Literature, Science and the Arts, 1975-1988 (Box 276)
          - Medical, 1975-1986 (Box 276)
          - Music, 1974-1984 (Box 276)
          - Natural Resources, 1975-1987 (Box 276)
          - Nursing, 1975-1988 (Box 276)
          - Pharmacy, 1975-1985 (Box 276)
          - Public Health, 1975-1984 (Box 276)
          - Rackham, 1979-1987 (Box 276)
          - Social Work, 1975-1986 (Box 276)
      - Foreign Students and Teaching Assistants, 1984; 1986; 1989 (Box 276)
      - Honor Codes, 1990; 1992 (Box 276)
      - Kleinsmith, Lewis (re: minorities in high schools), 1987-1990 (Box 276)
      - Pool Study (ACT), 1987 (Box 276)
      - Registrar, Office of the
        - General, 1988-1992 (Box 276)
        - Assisted Registration (for students with disabilities), 1991 (Box 276)
        - CRISP, 1986-1991 (Box 276)
        - Stuart, Al (Registrar), Meetings with, 1991-1992 (Box 276)
      - Residency, 1987-1991 (Box 276)
      - Scheduling (classroom space), 1987-1991 (Box 276)
      - Survey: Fiske Guide to Colleges, 1987-1991 (Box 276)
      - Swain, Mary Ann (Student Services)
        - General, 1990-1992 (Box 276)
        - Senior Management Team Meetings, 1991 (Box 276)
          (includes Student Services Evaluation Team)
      - Toledo, University of (course taught by Holmes:, 1990 (Box 276)
        (Introduction to Student Personnel Administration in Higher Education)
      - Tuition, 1985-1991 (Box 276)
    - 1982-1994, 1.1 linear feet
      - 7+1, 1994 (Box 391)
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Council (AAAC), 1993 (Box 391)
      - Academic Quality Consortium (AQC), 1994 (Box 391)
      - Academic Services Group (ASG), 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 391)
      - American Association for Higher Education (AAHE) Assessment and Quality Conference, 1994 (Box 391)
      - Business and Finance Seminar, 1993-1994 (Box 391)
      - Detroit Public Schools/UM Collaborative, 1991-1992 (Box 391)
      - IBM/Total Quality Management Proposal, 1992 (Box 391)
      - New Deans and Directors Meetings, 1993 (Box 391)
      - Planning Committee for a Computerized Academic Record, 1990; 4 folders (Box 391)
      - Registrar-Academic Record Project, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 391)
      - Registrar-Minority Audit, 1984-1991 (Box 391)
      - Total Quality, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 391)
      - United Coalition Against Racism (UCAR), 1990; 2 folders (Box 392)
      - Upper Room Trust Fund-Thomas Iden Scholarship, 1982-1995 (Box 392)
      - Vitae, 1995 (Box 392)
      - Workforce Alignment, 1993 (Box 392)
  - Chronological Files, 1981/82-1989
    - 1981/82-1986/87
      - 1981 (Box 111)
        - November-December, 2 folders (Box 111)
      - 1982
        - January-August, 8 folders (Box 111)
      - 1983
        - November-December, 2 folders (Box 111)
      - 1984
        - January (Box 111)
        - February-December, 10 folders (Box 112)
      - 1985
        - January-February, 2 folders (Box 112)
        - March-December, 10 folders (Box 113)
      - 1986
        - January-June, 6 folders (Box 113)
        - July-December, 6 folders (Box 114)
      - 1987
        - January-June, 6 folders (Box 114)
    - 1987-1988
      - 1987
        - July-December, 6 folders (Box 184)
      - 1988 (Box 185)
        - January-December, 12 folders (Box 185)
    - 1989
      - January-August, 1989, 10 folders (Box 244)
      - September-December, 1989, 7 folders (Box 245)
  - Schools and Colleges Files, 1982-1989
    - 1982-1989
      - Art, School of (Box 183)
      - Business Administration, School of (Box 183)
      - Dentistry, School of (Box 183)
      - Education, School of
        - General (Box 183)
        - Budget and Enrollment (Box 183)
        - Physical Education (Box 183)
      - Engineering, College of
        - Budget and Enrollment (Box 183)
        - Computer Fees (Box 183)
        - Minority Programs, 1980-1989 (Box 183)
      - Law, College of (Box 183)
      - Library Science, School of (Box 183)
      - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of
        - Biological Station (Box 183)
        - Budgets/Enrollment (Box 183)
        - English Language Institute (Box 183)
        - Enrollment (Box 183)
        - Honors Program, 1980-1988 (Box 183)
        - Inteflex (Box 183)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 183)
      - Medical School, HCOP/AIMED (Box 183)
      - Meeting Minutes (Dentistry, Graduate School, Intercollegiate Athletics, Law), 1975 (Box 184)
      - Music, School of (Box 184)
      - Natural Resources, School of
        - General (Box 184)
        - Budget, 1979-1984; 2 folders (Box 184)
      - Nursing, School of (Box 184)
      - Pharmacy, College of (Box 184)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General (Box 184)
        - Budget and Enrollment (Box 184)
      - Rackham School of Graduate Studies
        - General (Box 184)
        - Budget and Enrollment (Box 184)
        - Financial Aid, 1975-1983; 3 folders (Box 184)
      - Social Work, School of (Box 184)
  - M-Quality, 1990-1995; 2.7 linear feet
    - Ann Arbor Quality Week, 1995 (Box 392)
    - Awareness Survey, 1993 (Box 392)
    - Business Process Reengineering Meeting, 1993 (Box 392)
    - Changing Role of the Manager Course, 1993-1994 (Box 392)
    - Communications Task Force, 1992-1994 (Box 392)
    - Council of Independent Colleges (CIC) Meeting on Quality, 1993 (Box 392)
    - Council on Continuous Improvement, 1993-1995 (Box 392)
    - Design Team, 1991-1993 (Box 392)
    - Evaluation Committee, 1992-1994
      - Expenses, 1995 (Box 393)
    - Facilitator Training Sessions, 1992-1993 (Box 393)
    - Facilitators Network Meetings, 1993-1995; 2 folders (Box 393)
    - Flint, 1994 (Box 393)
    - Gopherblue, 1993-1995 (Box 393)
    - Human Resources Development (HRD), 1994-1995 (Box 393)
    - Implementation Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 393)
    - Implementation Task Force Subgroups, 1992-1993 (Box 393)
    - Innovators in Michigan Processes and Systems (IMPS), 1993-1994 (Box 393)
    - Kahn, Robert: "M-Quality: A Brief Intellectual History,", 1993-1994 (Box 393)
    - "M-Quality at the University of Michigan,", 1994 (Box 393)
    - M-Quality Expo, 1994-1995 (Box 393)
    - Multiculturalism, Diversity and M-Quality, 1994-1995 (Box 393)
    - Noel Levitz Speech, 1994 (Box 393)
    - Orientation Evaluations, 1992-1993 (Box 393)
    - Quality Improvement Teams (QIT) (2 of 4 folders), 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 393)
    - Quality Improvement Teams (2 of 4 folders), 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 394)
    - Qualtec, 1991-1995 (Box 394)
    - Record Articles, 1992-1995 (Box 394)
    - Regents Meeting Presentation, 1993 (Box 394)
    - Report Distribution Outside of UM, 1992-1993 (Box 394)
    - School of Natural Resources and the Environment, 1993 (Box 394)
    - Staff, 1993 (Box 394)
    - Steering Committee, 1993; 2 folders (Box 394)
    - Student involvement with M-Quality, 1993 (Box 394)
    - Surveys, 1994-1995 (Box 394)
    - Team Leader Training, 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 394)
    - Team Up for Community Service/Project Serve, 1995 (Box 394)
    - Total Quality Training for Deans and Directors, 1992 (Box 394)
    - Training Costs, 1992-1994 (Box 394)
    - Training Design Group (1 of 2 folders), 1992-1993 (Box 394)
    - Training Design Group (1 of 2 folders), 1993-1994 (Box 395)
    - UM Environmental Assessment Survey, 1993 (Box 395)
    - UM Medical Center
      - Costs, Benefits and Return from UMMC Total Quality Process, 1991 (Box 395)
      - Manager's Guide, 1991 (Box 395)
      - Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 395)
      - Quality and Diversity Task Force, 1994 (Box 395)
      - Total Quality Process Plan, 1991 (Box 395)
    - Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (VPCFO) Lead Team, 1992-1993 (Box 395)
- Sudarkasa, Niara
  As associate vice president from 1984 to 1986, Niara Sudarkasa was charged with leading the university's efforts in minority recruitment and retention. Prior to this appointment Sudarkasa had served as director of the Center for Afro-American and African Studies (CAAS) and was a professor of anthropology. She left the university in 1986 to become the first female president of Lincoln University.
  Sudarkasa's records comprise 6 linear feet and consist of three subseries: Personal Files, 1983-1986; Topical Files, 1983-1986; and Office of Minority Affairs Files, 1983-1987. Both the Topical Files and the Office of Minority Affairs Files contain extensive material on the topics of minority recruitment, enrollment and retention. The Topical Files also document Sudarkasa's role in the Tenure Issues Liaison Group.
  - Personal Files, 1983-1986
    - Appearances, Speeches, Articles (Box 65)
    - Biographical Materials (Box 65)
    - Correspondence (Box 65)
    - Resumes (Box 65)
    - Survey on Student Satisfaction (Box 65)
  - Topical Files, 1983-1986
    - Academic Affairs, Office of
      - Advisory Council (Box 65)
      - Executive Retreat (Box 65)
      - Faculty/Student Policy Cluster (Box 65)
      - Monday Brownbag Meetings (Box 65)
      - Policy Advisor (Box 65)
      - Staff Meetings (Box 65)
      - Sudarkasa's Role (Box 65)
      - Tenure Liaison Issues Group
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of, Tenure Proposal (Box 65)
        - Medical School Tenure Proposals (Box 65)
        - Meetings (Box 65)
        - Membership Lists (Box 65)
        - Personnel/Policy Cluster (Box 65)
        - Regents Actions (Box 65)
        - Tenure Proposal
          - Clippings (Box 65)
          - Drafts and discussion items, 2 folders (Box 65)
          - Meeting minutes of Sudarkasa (Box 66)
      - Tenure Proposal and the Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 66)
    - Academic Services Board (ASB) (Box 66)
    - Admissions
      - Admitted Students Who Declined to Attend the University of Michigan Survey, June 1986 (Box 66)
      - "Cancellation Survey of Midwest Black Students Admitted to the University of Michigan, Fall Term 1984" (by D. Robinson), September 1984 (Box 66)
      - Independent Inquiries from Students (Box 66)
      - Minority and Opportunity Recruitment Policies (Box 66)
      - Minority High School Recruitment, September 1984 (Box 66)
      - Minority Recruitment, Undergraduate, May-June 1985 (Box 66)
      - Minority Students (Box 66)
      - Review Panel, May 1984 (Box 66)
      - Queries Statistics (Box 66)
    - Admissions, Office of (Box 66)
    - Affirmative Action
      - Advisory Committee for Affirmative Action Programs (ACAAP) (Box 66)
      - Faculty Hiring (Box 66)
      - Handicapped Individuals (Box 66)
      - University of Michigan Policies (Box 66)
    - Affirmative Action Advisory Committee (Box 66)
    - Africa/Michigan: Partners In Trade (Box 66)
    - African Studies Association (Box 66)
    - Afro-American Association (Box 66)
    - American Anthropological Association (Box 66)
    - American Council on Education (ACE)
      - Advisory Board Successful Strategies for Increasing Minority Ph.D.s (Box 66)
      - General (Box 66)
      - Minority Concerns, Office of (Box 66)
      - National Identification Program (Box 66)
      - Post Tenure Evaluation Conference (Box 66)
    - American Museum of Natural History (Box 66)
    - Ann Arbor News (Box 66)
    - Anthropology, Department of
      - Joint Social Work-Anthropology Task Force Report, 1984 (Box 66)
      - Minority Recruitment (Box 66)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, Minority Recruitment (Box 66)
    - Art, School of, Minority Recruitment (Box 66)
    - Association of Black Anthropologists (Box 66)
    - Association of Social and Behavioral Scientists, Inc (Box 66)
    - Athletes, Class Scheduling of (Box 66)
    - Barbados African Diaspora Conference (Box 66)
    - Benin, National University of (Box 66)
    - Biology Study Center (includes report on lab's impact on minorities) (Box 66)
    - Biomedical Research Support Program for Minorities (Box 66)
    - Black Student Council, Proposal to Create (Box 66)
    - Black Student Psychological Association, Study of the Transition to College Life of the 1985 Minority Freshmen Proposal (draft), May 1985 (Box 66)
    - Black University of Michigan Graduates Reunions (Box 66)
    - Blacks in an Aging Society Conference (Box 66)
    - Business Administration, School of, Minority Recruitment (Box 66)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (Box 66)
    - Council for Minority Concerns (Box 66)